Today we’re going to make Shrimp and Scallop Fettucini with a side of garlic bread.
Okay, now we’ve got our seafood cut up, we have some beautiful Gulf shrimp, just, just about the perfect size for this, for me, you can use some really large ones if you like.
We’ve got the great diver’s scallops, again you can go ahead and just use the little scallops too, the Bay scallops which are like hundreds to the pound, but I like this for texture.
We’ve got a great sauce going so here’s how we are going to add this.
We have our beautiful shrimp, just grab your spoon and push it right in here and you’re going to see, as they say, they have a built-in thermometer, because this is what it’s going to show you, they’re going to turn pink after about two to three minutes depending on how high your heat is.
I like a nice simmer to put this in, because you really don’t want to overcook these.
And then go ahead and grab your scallops, as many as you like and just add those to the pan too.
See how beautifully white they are?
They’re going to become opaque and again you don’t want to overcook scallops either because they become tough.
But this is such a great medium for it; you know to put it into a broth type of thing or a sauce.
And they just cook really gently in there and they’re just going to be so tender and sweet along with the shrimp and all your other vegetables and spices and things that you’re just going to love this.